swattraffic.com 2019-06-24

# Swat Traffic

|   | 

  * Home
  * Login
  * Signup
  * Terms Of Service
  * Contact Support

|   | 

 Swat Traffic Terms

By registering for Swat Traffic you agree that you have read these terms, understand them, and agree to be bound by them.

Unless you received prior permission from Swat Traffic, you may only register for one Swat Traffic account.

You may not promote Swat Traffic in a way that could be considered spamming. You may only promote your referral URL and/or other promotional material in other traffic exchanges or advertising programs that allow it. Promoting Swat Traffic in a way that could be considered spamming will result in removal of your Swat Traffic account and possible legal action.

Users are completely responsible for the content they promote using Swat Traffic. Users are responsible for ensuring they have the rights to promote a URL, and any content it contains. Swat Traffic is not responsible if a user is in violation of another legal agreement, copyright infringement, or any other issues.

**URL Rules**

Before submitting a URL to Swat Traffic, please read these rules very carefully and make sure your URL does not violate any of them. If you violate any of these rules, your site will be deleted along with any credits assigned to them. Your Swat Traffic account may also be deleted.

*No sites with illegal activity.

*No frame-breaking sites.

*No viruses, trojans, or spyware.

*No adult content.

*  Rotators may be promoted only if all sites or banners in rotation comply with these terms. **Rotators within rotators are NOT acceptable** , and will cause your rotator URL to be suspended. Repeat offenders' accounts will be suspended after the second offense, regardless of member level. Please make a note of this. There are no exceptions allowed.

*No HYIPs or "investment autosurfs". These are illegal in most countries, including the United States.

*No PTP sites.

*Swat Traffic has the full right to delete any site that is inappropriate or questionable.

**Refund Policy**

All purchases made from Swat Traffic are considered final. The decision of whether a refund will be granted for a purchase is at the sole discretion of Swat Traffic.

 Swat Traffic Privacy Policy

Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At Swat Traffic, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe.   
Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.   
Definition of the Information Swat Traffic gathers and keeps track of.   
Swat Traffic gathers two types of information about users:   
1\. Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to receive more information on our services, special promotions or to receive our newsletter.   
2\. Information Swat Traffic gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers' needs and to help our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience. Because Swat Traffic derives its revenue mainly from its services, providing such aggregated demographic data is essential to keeping our services tailored to our users. Under no circumstances does Swat Traffic divulge any information about an individual user to a third party. 

Swat Traffic Gathers User Information In The Following Processes:  
OPTIONAL VOLUNTARY INFORMATION  
We offer the following free services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users:   
1\. Electronic newsletters (Dispatches)  
We will offer a free electronic newsletter to users. Swat Traffic gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management page. Users can also subscribe to the newsletters at the time of registration.   
2\. "E-mail this to a friend" Service  
Our site users can choose to electronically forward a link, page, or documents to someone else by clicking "e-mail this to a friend". The user must provide their email address, as well as that of the recipient. This information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the email. The information is not used for any other purpose.   
3\. Polling  
We may offer interactive polls to users so they can easily share their opinions with other users and see what our audience thinks about important issues. Opinions or other responses to polls are aggregated and are not identifiable to any particular user. Swat Traffic may use a system to "tag" users after they have voted, so they can vote only once on a particular question. This tag is not correlated with information about individual users.   
4\. Surveys  
Swat Traffic may occasionally conduct user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We never share any of this information about specific individuals with any third party.   
USAGE TRACKING  
Swat Traffic tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. Swat Traffic does break down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser).   
Swat Traffic sometimes tracks and catalogs the search terms that users enter in our Search function, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.   
COOKIES  
We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Swat Traffic uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). Our advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates.   
You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you do need cookies to participate actively in message boards, forums, polling and surveys.   
USE OF INFORMATION  
Swat Traffic uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.   
As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters and to enable users to participate in polls and surveys. We send out newsletters to subscribers on a regular schedule, and occasionally send out special editions when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing. Swat Traffic never shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers, sponsors or partners.   
When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We track search terms entered in Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don't track which terms a particular user enters.   
SHARING OF THE INFORMATION  
Swat Traffic uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience's demographics. This is essential to keeping our service free. We will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.   
SECURITY  
Swat Traffic operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers.   
OPT-OUT POLICY  
We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:   
1\. Opting not to register to receive our electronic newsletters.  
2\. Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our users   
YOUR CONSENT  
By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Swat Traffic. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

|    
---|---|---|---|---
